Seitz, Peter Arbitration Files 5733
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  Issue: Plant rules - mode of dress; arbitrability - contract silence. TR, SD, EX.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  Issue: Tardiness - discipline. TR, SD, EX.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  Issue: Classification of jobs. TR, SD, EX, RC.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - safety. TR, RC, SD.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  Issue: Alcoholism, Drinking, and Intoxication - drinking prior to reporting. TR, SD.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Ambridge Works, Ashland Works, Baltimore Operations, Kansas City Works including Union Wire Rope Department) vs. USA, Locals 1360, 1865, 3185, 13 and 2916, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  Issue: Past practice - Christmas bonus. (Award only).
- Armco Steel Corp., Advanced Materials Division, Baltimore Operations vs. USA, Local 3185, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  Issue: Layoff - lack of work; assignment of jobs change in location; layoff seniority; assignment of jobs seniority; discipline suspension; reporting pay lack of work; schedules of work notice; training and trial periods; employee rights ret
- Armco Steel Corp., Advanced Materials Division, Baltimore Operations vs. USA, Local 3185; Armco Steel Corp., Kansas City Works vs. USA, Local 13, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - inventory taking; discipline suspension; rates of pay time not worked; absences discipline; discrimination race; union representatives and business strikes, slowdowns and work stoppages; assignment of jobs - seniority
- Armco Steel Corp., Ambridge, Pennsylvania vs. USA, Local 1360; Armco Steel Corp., Advanced Materials Division vs. USA Local 3185; Armco Steel Corp., Ashland Works vs. USA, Local 1865, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  Issue: Discipline violation of plant rules; safety; Assignment of jobs - assignment of work outside bargaining unit; discipline suspension; discipline refusal to return to work; discipline discharge; incentive pay and incentive systems; vacancies
- Armco Steel Corp., Ashland Works vs. USA, Local 1865, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  Issue: Seniority - return of supervisors to bargaining unit; assignment of jobs; seniority supervisors and foremen; discipline discharge; discipline violation of plant rules; alcoholism, drinking and intoxication drinking prior to reporting. (Awar
- Armco Steel Corp., Ashland Works vs. USA, Local 1865; Houston Works vs. Local 2708; Kansas City Works vs. Local 13, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  Issue: Discipline discharge; discipline suspension; working conditions assignment of jobs; vacancies ability vs. seniority; assignment of jobs safety; discipline abuse of property; bidding denial of bid; discipline conviction of crime. (Aw
- Armco Steel Corp., Ashland Works vs. USA, Local 1865; Advanced Materials Division vs. Local 3185, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  Issue: Arbitrability - timeliness; classification of jobs - rates of pay; discipline discharge; bidding denial of bid; discipline suspension; classification of jobs; discipline negligence and carelessness; contracting out bargaining unit work; r
- Armco Steel Corp., Kansas City Works vs. USA, Local 2916, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  Issue: Lunch periods. (Award only).
- Arrow-Hart, Inc. vs. IAM, Lodge 19, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  Issue: Absences - unauthorized. (Award only).
- Associated Universities, Inc. (Brookhaven National Laboratory) vs. Directly Affiliated Local Union 24426, AFL-CIO, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  Issue: Classification of jobs - new classification. (Award only).
- Ball Brothers Co., Inc. (Atlantic Zinc Works Division) vs. USA, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Baltimore Sun (A.S. Abell Publishing Co.) vs. the Washington Baltimore Newspaper Guild, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  Issue: Arbitrability - timeliness; transfers - inter- departmental or inter-classification transfers. RC, SD, TR, EX.
- Barbizon Corp. (Barbizon of Utah, Inc.) vs. International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGWU), Local 161, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Issue: Reduction in force - economic reasons. (Award only).
- Bassick Co. vs. IUE, Local 229, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Issue: Absences discipline; layoff notice; rates of pay - transfers. (Award only).
- Bell Aircraft Corp. vs. UAW, Local 301, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Issue: Discipline - suspension; discipline - walkout. RC.
- Bell Telephone Co. of Pennsylvania vs. Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge; discipline suspension; vacations scheduling; arbitration procedure prior award, interpretation. (Award only).
- Bell Telephone Co. of Pennsylvania vs. Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania, 1976-1981 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  Issue: Transfers - bargaining unit work; vacations scheduling; discipline - discharge. (Award only).
- Bendix Corp., Communications Division, Towson, Maryland vs. IAM, Industrial Radio Lodge 1561; Electrical Components Division Sidney, New York vs. Sidney Lodge 1529, 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  Issue: Seniority layoff; fringe benefits pension plans. (Award only).
- Bendix Corp., Communications Division vs. IAM, Industrial Radio Lodge 1561, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  RC, B. (No award).
- Berlin and Jones Co., division of Harrison Blaine, Inc. vs. United Papermakers and Paperworkers (UPP), Local 292, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Issue: Layoff - seniority. (Award only).
- Beth-El Hospital vs. Joseph Gavurin, Victor Morales, Bernard Matthews and Jose Vargas, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Issue: Reinstatement - following work stoppage. (Award only).
- Beth Israel Medical Center vs. IBT, Local 814, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge. RC, B, EX, AN.
- Bethlehem Steel Co. vs. USA, Local 2604, 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  Issue: Past practice - assignment of jobs; Incentive pay and incentive systems; vacancies method of filling; discipline negligence and carelessness; assignment of jobs inventory taking, remedy for improper assignment. (Award only).
- Bethlehem Steel Co. vs. USA, Local 2602, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  Issue: Rates of pay; Apprentices, learners and trainees demotions; termination of employment imprisonment; Reinstatement - following illness or physical disability. (Award only).
- Beyer Products Co., Inc. vs. IBEW, Local 2074, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  Issue: Bidding - qualifications. (Award only).
- Bloomingdale Brothers, Inc. vs. Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union (RWDSU), District 65, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  Issue: Discipline - improper maintenance of records. (Award only).
- Bloomingdales vs. RWDSU, District 65, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  Issue: Transfers - management rights. (Award only).
- Boise Cascade Corp. vs. United Paperworkers International Union (UPIU), Local 286, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  Issue: Rates of pay. (Award only).
- Bond Baking Co. vs. Bakery and Confectionery Workers' International Union of America, Local 6, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  Issue: Rates of pay - increases; contracts - enforcement. (Award only).
- Booth Memorial Hospital vs. National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, RWDSU, District 1199, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  Issue: Holidays and holiday pay - part time employees. (Award only).
- Boston, City of vs. Service Employees International Union (SEIU), Local 285, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 18a)
  Withdrawn. RC.
- Boston Gear Incom International vs. USA, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  Cancelled. RC, B. (No award).
- Boston Herald Traveler Corp. vs. Newspaper Guild of Greater Boston, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Botany Cottons, Inc. vs. Textile Workers of America (UTWA), Local 1354, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  Issue: Contract Interpretation -rates of pay. (Award only).
- Bozzelli Brothers, Inc. vs. Laborers International Union of North America (LIUNA), Local 158, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  Issue: Fringe benefits - employer contributions. (Award only).
- BP Oil, Inc. vs. Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAW), Local 8-337, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  Issue: Termination of employment - following illness or physical disability; grievance and grievance procedure - timeliness. (Award only).
- Breinig Brothers vs. OCAW, Local 13-510, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  Issue: Arbitrability - grievance procedure - failure to follow. (Award only).
- Bridgeport Board of Education vs. Bridgeport Education Association, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - added duties. (Award only).
- Bridgeport, University of vs. American Association of University Professors (AAUP), University of Bridgeport Chapter, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  Issue: Layoff - notice. (Award only).
- Brink's Incorporated vs. IBT, Local 820, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Bristol Board of Education vs. Bristol Federation of Teachers, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  Issue: Arbitrability - contract interpretation; rates of pay. (Award only).
- Bristol Township School Districts vs. Bristol Township Education Association, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  RC, B, EX. (No award).
- Broadcast Plaza, Inc. vs. National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians (NABET), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Broadway Resources, Inc. vs. Screen Actors' Guild, 1979-1983 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  Issue: Contracts - enforcement. B, RC, AN, EX.
- Brock-Hall Dairy Co. vs. United Independent Dairy Workers of America, Inc., 1961 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - supervisors. (Award only).
- Bronx Hospital vs. Joseph E. Brown, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  Issue: Fights and altercations - reinstatement. (Award only).
- Brooklyn Borough Gas Co. vs. IBEW, Local 1869, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  Issue: Past practice - working conditions. (Award only).
- Browne and Sharpe Manufacturing Co. vs. American Federation of Technical Engineers, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Budd Co. vs. UTWA, Local 266, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  Issue: Overtime - assignment of jobs. (Award only).
- Buffalo, City of - Board of Education vs. Buffalo Teachers' Federation, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  Issue: Leaves of absence - maternity leave. (Award only).
- Buffalo Courier-Express, Inc. vs. the Newspaper Guild of Buffalo, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  Issue: Vacancies. (Award only).
- Buffalo Tank Corp. vs. USA, Local 4493, Local 3734, 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  Issue: Seniority promotions; Rates of pay assignment of jobs; seniority ability vs. seniority; alcoholism, drinking and intoxication burden of proof; assignment of jobs past practice. (Award only).
- Burnham Corp. vs. USA, Local 2555, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  Issue: Classification of jobs - rates of pay. (Award only).
- Butler Aviation - La Guardia, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 277, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  Issue: Insubordination - discipline. (Award only).
- Carousel Theatre Inc. vs. Actors Equity Association in Behalf of Member George Liker, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  Issue: Discipline. (Award only).
- Celanese Corp. of America vs. Textile Workers Union of America, Local 1093, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - past practice. (Award only).
- Cerro Wire and Cable Co. vs. IBEW, Local 3, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Chandler Evans, Inc. vs. UAW, Unity Lodge, Local 405, 1975-1980 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  Issue: Discipline suspension; insubordination discipline; management rights working rules. (Award only).
- Chandler Evans, Inc. vs. UAW, Unity Lodge, Local 405, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  Issue: Management rights - working conditions; past practice. RC, B, EX, SD. (No award).
- Chandler Evans, Inc. vs. UAW, Unity Lodge, Local 405, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge; absences - leaving plant or work area without permission. B, RC, AN, EX, SD.
- Chapman Valve Manufacturing Company vs. IUE, Local 278, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  Issue: Absences - discipline. (Award only).
- Chestnut Hill Bus Corp. vs. ATU, Local Division 1336, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  Issue: Arbitrability - waiver; discipline - discharge.
- Citizens Gas and Coke Utility, Indianapolis, Indiana vs. IBEW, Local 1400, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Claridge Hotel Casino vs. Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union, Local 54, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Clemmey, John L., Co. vs. USA, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Colt Industries, Firearms Division vs. UAW, Local 376, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  Issue: Absences - excessive. (Award only).
- Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc. vs. Directors Guild of America, Inc., 1961 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  Issue: Discipline - substandard performance. (Award only).
- Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc. vs. Directors Guild of America, Inc., 1961 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Columbia University in the City of New York vs. Transport Workers Union of America (TWU), Local 241, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Columbus Coated Fabrics vs. Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU), Local 487-T, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Commonwealth International, Inc. vs. Warehouse Employees, Local 169, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  Issue: Discipline - violation of plant rules. (Award only).
- Commonwealth Water Co. vs. Utility Workers Union of America, Local 391, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  Issue: Rates of pay - increases. (Award only).
- Conant Ball Co. vs. United Furniture Workers of America, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  Issue: Rates of pay - piecework. (Award only).
- Conde Nast Publications, Inc. vs. International Typographical Union, Local 503, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  Issue: Rates of pay - holiday. (Award only).
- Connecticut Opera Association vs. American Guild of Musical Artists, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  Issue: Rates of pay - guaranteed rate - contract interpretation.
- Consolidated Diesel Electric Co. vs. UAW, Local 259, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - strikes, slowdowns and work stoppages - walk out. (Award only).
- Container Corp. of America vs. International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers (IBFO), Local 473, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  Issue: Suspension - plant rules - no smoking rule. AN, RC, B, EX, SD. (No award).
- Continental Can Co. (Houston Plant 38) vs. USA, Local 2282, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  Issue: Rates of pay - classification of job. (Award only).
- Continental Can Co. (Milwaukee Plant 77) vs. USA, Local 4454, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  Issue: Discipline - layoff - classification of job. (Award only).
- Continental Can Co. St. Lous Plant 73 vs USA Local 1120; Los Angeles Plant 11 vs Local 1502; Terminal Island Plant 76 vs Local 5303; Toronto Plant 54 vs Local 4025; Paterson Plant 48 vs Local 3913; Baltimore Plant 16 vs Local 5139., 1957 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  Issue: Classification of jobs - elimination of jobs; bargaining units - contracting out; discipline - suspension, plant rules; shift scheduling - irregular shift, rates of pay; rates of pay - time not worked; rates of pay - holidays, past practice. (Award
- Continental Can Co. Syracuse Plant 1 vs USA, Local 3342; St. Lous Plant 73 vs Local 1120; Milwaukee Plant 77 vs. Local 4454., 1957 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  Issue: Shift scheduling; rates of pay - holiday pay; classification of jobs - work outside classification; grievance procedure - timeliness; rates of pay - temporary position; discipline - layoff.
- Continental-Diamond Fibre Corp., Bridgeport Plant vs. UTWA, Local 58, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  Issue: Demotions. (Award only).
- Conver Steel and Wire Co., Inc. vs. IBT, Steel, Metal, Alloys and Hardware Fabricators and Warehousemen, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - downgrading. (Award only).
- Conwed Corp. vs. USA, District 9, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge; discipline suspension; schedules of work - seniority. (Award only).
- Cornish Wire Co. vs. IUE, Local 299, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  Issue: Arbitrability - timeliness; rates of pay - transfers; safety. (Award only).
- Cornwall, Town Board of vs. Tri-County Federation of Police, Cornwall Town Unit, Town Police, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  Issue: Contract interpretation. (Award only).
- Crescent Insulated Wire and Cable Co., Inc. vs. IBEW, Local 1130, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  Issue: Discipline - refusal of overtime. (Award only).
- Crown Reproductions, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 966, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 75)
- Curtiss-Wright Corp. vs. IAM, Local 703; vs. UAW Local 300; vs. Office Employees International Union Local 212, 1958-1960 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Issue: Carelessness and negligence discharge; plant rules intermarriage of employees; absences dual employment; overtime call in; classification of job downgrading; assignment of jobs bargaining unit work; classification of jobs rates of pay
- Curtiss-Wright Corp. vs. UAW, Local 300, Local 1223, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Issue: Classification of jobs - change in work assignments; rates of pay higher classification; rates of pay call in, plant closed at report time; classification of jobs work outside classification; assignment of jobs - seniority. (Award only).
- Curtiss-Wright Corp. vs. UAW, Local 300; vs. IAM, Local 703, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Issue: Discharge - absences, excessive; classification of jobs elimination of job duties; discipline leaving work area without permission; classification of jobs transfer of duties. (Award only).
- Curtiss-Wright Corp. vs. UAW, Local 300; vs. IAM Local 703, 1958-1961 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Issue: Demotion; rates of pay after layoff; seniority; overtime equalization; discharge incompetence; classification of jobs added duties; classification of jobs elimination of duties; Illness sick pay. (Award only).
- Curtiss-Wright Corp. vs. UAW, Local 300; vs. IAM, Local 703, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Issue: Absences excessive; Discharge incompetence; assignment of jobs; discharge excessive absences; classification of jobs assignment of work outside classification. (Award only).
- Curtiss-Wright Corp. vs. IAM, Local 703; vs. UAW Local 300, 1961-1963 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Issue: Seniority; discipline discharge, excessive absences; demotion; excessive absences; incompetence; discharge unsatisfactory performance; discipline suspension, carelessness. (Award only).
- Danbury Hospital vs. Connecticut Health Care Associates, Unit 47, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Issue: Shift scheduling. (Award only).
- Darien Board of Education vs. Darien Education Association, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Issue: Rates of pay - pay below contract rate. (Award only).
- Davega Stores vs. RWDSU, District 65, 1960-1961 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge incompetence, insubordination, theft; layoff - absences. (Award only).
- Day-Jewish Journal vs. Newspaper Guild of New York, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  Issue: Layoff - absences. (Award only).
- Delaware County Daily Times vs. Newspaper Guild of Greater Philadelphia, Local 10, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  Issue: Discipline - suspension - insubordination. TR, AN, B, EX, SD, RC. (No award).
- Delaware County Daily Times vs. Newspaper Guild of Greater Philadelphia, Local 10, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Delaware County Daily Times vs. Newspaper Guild of Greater Philadelphia, Local 10, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Delaware County Daily Times vs. Newspaper Guild of Greater Philadelphia, Local 10, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Delmarva Power and Light Co. vs. IBEW, Local 1238, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  Issue: Contracting out - janitorial services. (Award only).
- Desimone, A. J., Corp. vs. Fabricating and Production Workers Union, Local 299, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - carelessness and negligence. (Award only).
- Detroit Steel Corp. vs. USA, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  Issue: Shift scheduling - cancellation. (Award only).
- Dick, A. B., Co. vs. IUE, Local 459, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  Issue: Union representation; unit determination. TR, RC, B, EX, SD. (No award).
- Dictaphone Corp. vs. IUE, Local 459, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  Issue: Promotion - seniority. (Award only).
- DiMarcantonio, James, vs. Flower and Fifth Avenue Hospitals, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  Issue: Reinstatement, refusal - strikes. (Award only).
- DiSabatino, Ernest, and Sons vs. Operating Engineers, Local 542, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  Issue: Plant rules - Nonenforcement - unauthorized use of company property. RC, B, EX, AN, SD.
- Diversified Maintenance, Inc. vs. SEIU, Local 36, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  Withdrawn. B, RC.
- Domglas, Inc. vs. Glass Bottle Blowers Association of the United States and Canada (GBBA), 1982 (Box 6, Folder 22a)
- Donner-Hanna Coke Corp. vs. USA, Local 2268, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  Issue: Promotion; safety; carelessness and negligence; classification of jobs. (Award only).
- Downingtown Paper Co. vs. International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  Issue: Classification of jobs - elimination of jobs. (Award only).
- Drake Hotel vs. Hotel and Restaurant Employees, Local 274, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  Issue: Layoff - remedy for improper layoff. (Award only).
- Dukeland Nursing Home vs. National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, Local 1199E, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - insubordination.
- Dumont - Division of Thomson vs. IUE, Local 420, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  Issue: Timeliness - grievance; posting - new classification. (Award only).
- Dumont - Division of Thomson vs. IUE, Local 420, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  Issue: Classification of jobs - assignment of work outside classification - shutdown. (Award only).
- Dumont - Division of Thomson vs. IUE, Local 420, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  Issue: Classification of jobs - duties performed. (Award only).
- Dumont - Division of Thomson vs. IUE, Local 420, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  Issue: Assignment of job. (Award only).
- Dupont vs. Dupont Employees Philadelphia Works Union, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs - bargaining unit work. SD.
- Dupont vs. Fairfield Employees Association, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  Issue: Rates of pay - time not worked - weather conditions. (Award only).
- Dupont vs. Chemical Workers Association; vs. Federation of DuPont Independent Union, Dupont System; vs. ICW Local 527, 1976-1980 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  Issue: Discipline - suspension insubordination; discharge absences, tardiness; promotion - seniority. (Award only).
- Dupont vs. Chemical Workers Association, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  Withdrawn.
- Dupont vs. Chemical Workers Association, Inc., 1983 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  Issue: Apprentices - reduction in force. TR, SD, RC, B, EX, AN.
- Eastern Co., Alloy Foundries Division vs. USA, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge - improper personal conduct. (Award only).
- Eastern Airlines, Inc. vs. IAM, District 100, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge theft, absences, improper job attitude, falsification of records, excessive absences. (Award only).
- El Diario Publishing Co. vs. New York Mailers Union Number 6, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  Issue: Severance pay. (Award only).
- Electric Storage Battery Co. vs IUE, Local 265; Electrol, Inc. vs IAM, Local 1512; Ellenville Central School District vs Ellenville Teachers Association; Englewood Hospital Association vs Hospital Professional and Allied Employees, 1961-1980 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  Issue: Discipline - suspension, discharge - insubordination, leaving work area without permission; contract interpretation; shift scheduling - management rights. (Award Only.)
- Evans Amityville Dairy, Inc. vs Milk Drivers and Dairy Employees Local 584; Evanston, City of vs International Association of Firefighters, 1962-1974 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  Issue: Discipline - suspension, misconduct; arbitration procedure - contract dispute. (Award Only.)